♪Eager to change the planet's orbit♪
حريص على تغيير مدار الكوكب
♪Unexpectedly, you've become the planned orbit♪
♪ بشكل غير متوقع ، لقد أصبحت المدار المخطط
♪I can't avoid the end designated by you♪
♪ لا أستطيع تجنب النهاية التي حددتها لك ♪
♪Yet you're nowhere to be seen♪
♪ ومع ذلك فأنت لست في أي مكان يمكن رؤيته
♪I'm determined to look for your trace♪
♪ أنا مصمم على البحث عن أثرك ♪
♪At last, I turned into an unknown star♪
♪ أخيرًا تحولت إلى نجم غير معروف
♪Wandering silently on the edge of the Milky Way♪
♪ تتجول بصمت على حافة درب التبانة
♪Still, I can't see you♪
♪ ما زلت لا أستطيع رؤيتك
♪How to get rid of your gravity♪
♪ كيف تتخلص من جاذبيتك ♪
♪I'm both fascinated and suffocated♪
♪ أنا مفتون ومختنق على حد سواء
♪The cycle is disturbed and the flight is out of control♪
الدورة مضطربة والرحلة خارجة عن السيطرة
♪Eager to crash on the earth with a shooting star♪
♪ حريصة على الاصطدام على الأرض مع شهاب
♪How to counteract your gravity♪
♪ كيفية مواجهة جاذبيتك ♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
ابتعد عن كل بُعد ♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪ انسى كل شيء قبل أن أغرق
♪Even though I don't know my own whereabouts♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف مكاني ♪
=Yan Zhi's Romantic Story=
= قصة رومانسية يان تشي =
=Episode 15=
= الحلقة 15 =
(Dad 16 missed calls)
(مكالمات أبي 16 الفائتة)
Shen Zhizhou,
شين تشيتشو
do you know Mr. Lin's position in the circle?
هل تعرف موقع السيد لين في الدائرة؟
Do you want to make a movie or not?
هل تريد أن تصنع فيلما أم لا؟
Yes, I admit it.
نعم ، أنا أعترف بذلك.
I didn't arrange the dinner just for your movie.
لم أرتب العشاء فقط لفيلمك.
I want you to meet Lin Ya.
أريدك أن تقابل لين يا.
From a respectable family, she used to study at a famous university abroad.
من عائلة محترمة ، كانت تدرس في جامعة مشهورة بالخارج.
No matter on character, appearance, or manner,
بغض النظر عن الشخصية أو المظهر أو الطريقة ،
she is better than Yan Ning.
إنها أفضل من يان نينغ.
What about you?
وماذا عنك؟
Where was your manner?
اين كان طريقتك
You didn't even say hi.
أنت لم تقل مرحبا.
How could you embarrass me like that?
كيف تحرجني هكذا؟
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
don't be pertinaciously stupid.
لا تكن غبيًا عنيدًا.
OK.
نعم.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I said, OK.
قلت: حسنا.
You...
أنت...
Yan Ning doesn't like me.
يان نينغ لا يحبني.
We'll never be together.
لن نكون معًا أبدًا.
Are you satisfied?
هل أنت راض؟
How are you feeling?
كيف تشعر؟
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
36.1℃. The fever has gone.
36.1 ℃.  ذهبت الحمى.
Sit here.
اجلس هنا.
I'll get you a cup of water.
سأحضر لك كوب ماء.
Yeah.
نعم.
You'd better take a day off today.
من الأفضل أن تأخذ يوم إجازة اليوم.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
I can shoot today.
يمكنني التصوير اليوم.
Yan Ning, did you cook porridge?
يان نينغ ، هل طهيت العصيدة؟
Didn't I tell you to call me?
ألم أقل لك أن تتصل بي؟
Why did you cook porridge yourself?
لماذا قمت بطهي العصيدة بنفسك؟
What porridge?
ما عصيدة؟
Here, see for yourself.
هنا ، انظر بنفسك.
It was overcooked.
كان مطبوخا أكثر من اللازم.
Look at you. I told you
انظر لحالك.  أخبرتك
I should stay and take care of you,
يجب أن أبقى وأعتني بك ،
but you wouldn't let me.
لكنك لن تدعني.
In the end, you had to cook porridge yourself.
في النهاية ، كان عليك طهي العصيدة بنفسك.
Yan Ning.
يان نينغ.
Here. Hot water.
هنا.  ماء ساخن.
You've just got better. Get more rest.
لقد تحسنت للتو.  احصل على قسط أكبر من الراحة.
And be careful not to catch a cold.
واحرص على عدم الإصابة بنزلة برد.
Wait.
انتظر.
What's wrong?
ماالخطب؟
Gu Han, I have something to tell you.
قو هان ، لدي شيء أقوله لك.
I'm listening.
أنا أستمع.
- Actually, I... - Yan Ning.
- في الواقع ، أنا ... - يان نينغ.
We're in trouble, Yan Ning!
نحن في ورطة ، يان نينغ!
Look.
نظرة.
Yan Ning, the aloof muse, becomes a cheating muse.
أصبح يان نينغ ، الملهم المنعزل ، ملهمًا للغش.
Dating Gu Han sweetly doesn't stop her
مواعدة غو هان بلطف لا يمنعها
from throwing herself at the director.
من إلقاء نفسها على المخرج.
Her innocent image has collapsed completely.
انهارت صورتها البريئة تماما.
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
what happened between you and Shen Zhizhou?
ماذا حدث بينك وبين شين تشيتشو؟
It's a misunderstanding,
إنه سوء فهم ،
but he did express his feelings for me.
لكنه عبر عن مشاعره تجاهي.
What?
لما؟
Did you say yes?
هل قلت نعم
I didn't.
لم أكن.
You and Gu Han are a popular couple now.
أنت وغو هان زوجان مشهوران الآن.
The rumors about your love affair with Shen Zhizhou
الشائعات حول علاقة حبك مع شين تشيتشو
will be a heavy blow to your image.
ستكون ضربة قوية لصورتك.
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
I can help.
يمكنني المساعدة.
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
as long as we announce that
طالما نعلن ذلك
we are officially dating,
نحن نتواعد رسميًا ،
the rumors will be scotched
الشائعات ستُحبط
and the show will be more popular.
وسيكون العرض أكثر شهرة.
Gu Han, you must think it through.
قو هان ، يجب أن تفكر في الأمر جيدًا.
- If you officially announce... - At this time,
- إذا أعلنت رسميًا ... - في هذا الوقت ،
nothing is more important than Yan Ning.
لا شيء أهم من يان نينغ.
I object.
أعترض.
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
this is probably the best way to solve the problem
ربما تكون هذه هي أفضل طريقة لحل المشكلة
- And you've always... - Yan Ning.
- وأنت دائما ... - يان نينغ.
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن هذا
It's my pleasure.
أنه من دواعي سروري.
Qiu Wen,
تشيو ون ،
would you give us a minute?
هل من الممكن أن تعطينا دقيقة؟
Yes.
نعم.
Gu Han,
جو هان
I was about to tell you this morning.
كنت على وشك إخبارك هذا الصباح.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Don't we get along well on the show?
ألا نتفق جيدًا في العرض؟
And you've told me about your opinions.
وقد أخبرتني عن آرائك.
Now we just need to settle it in advance.
الآن نحتاج فقط إلى تسوية الأمر مقدمًا.
Gu Han,
جو هان
you're a perfect dating partner.
أنت شريك مواعدة مثالي.
Being with you, either in private
التواجد معك سواء على انفراد
or at work, makes me happy.
أو في العمل ، يسعدني.
I thought I fell for you.
ظننت أنني وقعت في حبك.
I've tried countless times
لقد حاولت مرات لا تحصى
to let you into my heart
لأدعك تدخل قلبي
and fall for you for real.
ويقع في حبك على أرض الواقع.
But I've realized today that
لكني أدركت ذلك اليوم
I like you instead of loving you.
أنا معجب بك بدلاً من أن أحبك.
Gu Han, I'm sorry.
جو هان ، أنا آسف.
I should say sorry.
يجب أن أقول آسف.
I'm too impatient.
أنا شديد الصبر.
Yan Ning, I promise, next time I'll...
يان نينغ ، أعدك ، في المرة القادمة سوف ...
Gu Han,
جو هان
I've made up my mind.
أنا إتخذت قراري.
I'll quit the show.
سأترك العرض.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I won't give up.
أنا لن أستسلم.
I believe that one day,
أعتقد أنه يومًا ما ،
you'll fall for me.
ستقع من أجلي.
Hello, Zhizhou.
مرحبا تشيتشو.
Dad, did you do that?
أبي ، هل فعلت ذلك؟
Without your instruction,
بدون تعليماتك ،
entertainment reporters won't release the news about my love affair.
لن ينشر الصحفيون الترفيهيون الأخبار المتعلقة بعلاقة حبي.
I told you clearly that
قلت لك ذلك بوضوح
Yan Ning didn't like me at all.
لم يعجبني يان نينغ على الإطلاق.
Why don't you give her a break?
لماذا لا تعطيها استراحة؟
Because you care too much about her.
لأنك تهتم بها كثيرا.
For her, you even gave up the chance to make your own movie,
بالنسبة لها ، حتى أنك تخلت عن فرصة صنع فيلمك الخاص ،
right?
حق؟
I can't let her ruin you.
لا أستطيع تركها تدمرك.
Dad,
أب،
I won't let you manipulate me again.
لن أسمح لك بالتلاعب بي مرة أخرى.
Mr. Shen, Mr. Shen.
السيد شين ، السيد شين.
We have a few questions for you.
لدينا بعض الأسئلة لك.
Mr. Shen, do you really have a love affair with Yan Ning?
سيد شين ، هل حقا لديك علاقة حب مع يان نينغ؟
As the director of the show,
بصفته مدير العرض ،
how can you date a guest?
كيف يمكنك مواعدة ضيف؟
Did you give her the chance
هل منحتها الفرصة
to be on the show?
لتكون في العرض؟
Mr. Shen, please answer us.
السيد شين ، من فضلك أجبنا.
I'll give you a short answer.
سأعطيك إجابة قصيرة.
I don't have an affair with Yan Ning.
ليس لدي علاقة مع يان نينغ.
I was the one who pestered her.
كنت أنا من أزعجها.
I like her.
انا معجب بها.
I like her so much
أحب لها كثيرا
that I'm jealous of her relationship with Gu Han.
أنني أشعر بالغيرة من علاقتها مع جو هان.
After the incident,
بعد الحادث ،
I'll take the blame
سآخذ اللوم
and resign from the show.
والاستقالة من العرض.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Mr. Shen, Mr. Shen, then the show...
السيد شين ، السيد شين ، ثم العرض ...
♪The past is scattered all over the place♪
الماضي مبعثر في كل مكان
♪I remained where I was and waited for you♪
♪ بقيت حيث كنت وانتظرتك ♪
♪Doing my one-man show♪
♪ القيام ببرنامجي الفردي ♪
♪The deeper the scar, the more involved I am♪
♪ كلما كانت الندبة أعمق ، كنت أكثر انخراطًا
♪The more I try to forget, the more I miss you♪
♪ كلما حاولت أن أنسى ، اشتقت إليك أكثر
♪Losing you♪
خسارتك ♪
♪I sunk in there myself♪
♪ غرقت هناك بنفسي ♪
♪I crash on an isolated island♪
♪ تحطمت على جزيرة معزولة ♪
♪Covered in scars, I need the antidote, while the rain is pouring♪
مغطاة بالندوب ، أحتاج إلى الترياق ، بينما المطر ينهمر ♪
♪You don't care about the thing I treasure most♪
♪ أنت لا تهتم بالشيء الذي أعتز به أكثر
♪In an instant my heartbeat is frozen♪
♪ في لحظة تجمد دقات قلبي ♪
♪Broken pride♪
كبرياء مكسور
♪Once impulsive, then regretful, does it matter♪
بمجرد الاندفاع ، ثم الندم ، فهل يهم
♪You turn around, leaving me nowhere to go♪
♪ تستدير ، تاركة لي مكانًا أذهب إليه
♪Be your disciple and beg for love♪
♪ كن تلميذك واستجداء الحب ♪
♪Broken pride♪
كبرياء مكسور
♪Once impulsive, then regretful, does it matter♪
بمجرد الاندفاع ، ثم الندم ، فهل يهم
♪You turn around, leaving me nowhere to go♪
♪ تستدير ، تاركة لي مكانًا أذهب إليه
♪Be your disciple and beg for love♪
♪ كن تلميذك واستجداء الحب ♪
=Yan Zhi's Romantic Story=
= قصة رومانسية يان تشي =
(The right of communication through network)
(حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة)
(is exclusively owned by Tencent)
(مملوكة حصريًا لشركة Tencent)